Music
Thank you for watching
Welcome!
No, no, no, welcome.
Welcome. We don't have a store or anything.
Then what are you doing?
So, today...
The Doll's Festival is coming up.
Well, as you can see...
We're here at the cooking studio.
Yay.
Lovely.
Kaname, please explain.
This time, I think we've made two things.
I think we've made two things with this group.
First, three-color pudding.
Three colors?
Three colors.
No, no, no, I don't know.
I can't think of any.
Why three colors?
Well, I'm going to make one later.
What colors?
I don't know. I'll figure it out.
Shut up about the middle!
It's the middle that's holding us back.
It's the Doll's Festival, so shouldn't it start with the Doll's Festival?
No, it doesn't start with the Girls' Festival.
That's why the first one...
It's not going anywhere?
No, it doesn't.
Okay, the other one.
Cupcakes.
Cupcake.
Pudding. Pudding.
Oh, that's a good one. Oh, that's a good one.
Let's hear it for one pudding, two cupcakes.
Yes, whichever you want to say.
Okay, one pudding.
Yes, sir.
Three puddings, three puddings?
Three-color pudding sounds good.
We'll do pudding.
We'll do team pudding.
Team Pudding.
Okay, let's split up our team, and there you go.
We're Team Cup Cup.
Oh, hey, Kanabe laughed.
Kanabe
What do you do in Cup of Cups?
What does Team Cup Cup do?
Up to 160 seconds.
I see.
Well, let's do this.
One, two, three, four.
That's 37.
Okay. Okay.
One hundred and sixty.
Next, 1, 2, 3, 4
OK.
I'll take the pink.
Yay.
Here you go.
Just a little tilt and you're good to go.
Oh!
Sounds good.
It's getting hard already.
Blow on it. Blow on it.
Blow on it.
There's a mix up.
24 hours later, please.
It's all mixed in.
The whipped cream is still the same.
But I'm fine.
Come on, come on, come on.
Go on, go on, go on.
Go on, go on, go on, go on!
I don't know where I'm going with this.
Till we get to the corner.
Can I rush you one more time?
Granulated sugar.
So I can put it in this?
Is it Haklik?
I'm gonna go take another look.
What was it?
Wait a minute.
These four...
I just saw them.
I forgot everything.
Crack the eggs into another bowl
Add the granulated sugar.
With a hand mixer, fluff to a white consistency
Mix.
Voila!
Yee-hah!
Ya-ya!
Oh, that's good.
Wait for this, Kazuto.
How long do I have to do this?
Beat until white and fluffy.
Yes, okay.
Here.
How is it?
Yes, it's done.
Hmm? No? Hmm? No?
And then they mix it with this here.
I understand. Okay, let's put it in once.
Okay, 3 minutes, done!
It's fun!
Cooking is fun!
As expected, as expected
That's what I'm talking about.
Why are you laughing?
So, from here, here.
I'll put this in. Put this in here, already.
And put in the baking powder here.
And mix it in.
Now we're at the end of the process. Why don't we take the baking powder and put it in here.
Okay, first, put this in here.
I'm going to put this in first.
Oh, my God, you're such a measuring stick man.
You're gonna do this much?
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, no, no, no...
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, well, well, well...
Oh, oh, 100 grams!
100 grams. That's good, right?
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Okay.
One hundred and eighty grams.
And baking powder.
Baking powder.
Two.
But baking powder, this is it, definitely.
Two grams.
A teaspoon... two thirds.
I can do this later.
A teaspoon. Which championship?
Oh!Oh!
It's a...
A teaspoon, right?
Yes, sir.
Which championship teaspoon?
5cc... 7.5cc...
Teaspoon... 5ml?
Isn't that a teaspoon?
Then this one.
5?
5cc...
That's it.
Yes, it's a misspelling.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Does that mean...?
That means...
You're back.
Why?
You know why? This.
This is my...
I didn't know I had this.
It's too hard.
This is too hard.
Okay, so...
2 teaspoons...
Yes, please, put it on.
Oh, and...
Not this one?
Yes, so where do you stick it?
Yes, gelatin...
Thank you very much.
Blow on it.
Well, I'll just turn it on once.
I'll be scared if it comes flying out.
Here's some sugar...
Oh, that's good.
That's nice.
That's nice. Great.
I'd better do it early.
Sugar...
1 tablespoon.
No, but yeah, yeah.
No, wait, maybe heat. See?
Heat...
If you can get it to melt with the heat...
Oh, wow.
There's matcha.
Okay, well, put the gelatin down for now.
Milk meat.
Milk...
Matcha...
Uh...
A teaspoon. A quarter.
That's very little.
It's not that much...
Excuse me.
Is this okay?
I've never made sweets before.
No.
You mean you've cooked for us before, but not for sweets anymore?
But not sweets anymore?
Yeah.
So yellow...
Okay, you can mix it up now.
Is that okay?
Yeah. - Okay.
Yeah, it's good.
Sure.
Okay. One tablespoon.
You didn't open the hot water, did you?
Uh, actually...
Oh, it's open, it's open, it's open.
Uh, uh, one tablespoon. Uh, let's see... 1 tablespoon
A tablespoon... a tablespoon of...
Uh, yeah, uh, okay.
Yes, sir.
Into the mix.
Put it in.
Shhh, it's in there.
Oh, no, not again...
Keep going, matched
Daily gj
Then we'll live.
We need to put it on there.
I'll put it on the weight system.
You know what I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah!
I couldn't miss it.
Mix this in quickly.
When it's melted, put it in this mixture and mix it in.
Mix it up fast.
Here we go.
I'm starting to feel like a senior.
Okay, first of all, mix it quickly.
I'm going to go get my own shell.
I'm home.
How do you get the shells off in such a clean way?
That's good.
Quicker.
Good.
Fine.
See you in the next video.
And then we're going to put about four ice cubes
Put them in the ice.
Leave them there.
Put them around here.
We're gonna eat around here, and then we'll go home.
Let's use the hand mixer again.
I'll wash it. Then I'll wash it.
Do it.
Yes, in advance.
What kind of ice?
Wait for the hand mixer.
Wait.
I'll wait a moment.
Please.
Keep mixing until the ice comes.
Usual cooking
Wait, I got this.
I'm making the green, you do the white.
Now do yellow.
Do the same thing.
Okay, well, I'll just get it ready.
I don't know.
Let's get the white one ready.
That's it.
But...
We just bought them together.
This is Bonka's too.
This is all we have.
A cup will do.
It works with a cup.
A cup.
70 grams.
Seems to be easy to make weights.
Seventy.
Let's try 70.
All right.
70 is easy!
This is it.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'll mix it up.
Here we go!
Try 70.
Just this once. It's just this one time.
One time.
Two times.
Three times.
Four times.
Only 5 times
Only 6 times
Only 7 times
Only six times
Only seven times
Only 7 times
Only 10 times
12 times
12 pieces
13 pieces
14 pieces
15 pcs
16 pcs
17 pcs.
18 pcs
19 cupcakes
I'm making cupcakes today.
I don't have paper cupcakes.
Yes.
See you next week! See you next week!
Yahana. That much?
It's not that much!
Yahana, the ice is out.
Thank you.
Where is it?
Is this it?
Green.
Yahana, pour some ice on the green.
Pour some ice.
Put the cake on it.
Yay!
Reina, ah! Rein-ah! Aah!
Reina, come on!
Reina, come here, come here!
Good night.
Ei!
When you come, mix until the ice is small.
Let's do this for the rest of our lives.
Hot water is hot water
Once you get the sugar right...
You didn't put any sugar in it.
Is that it?
I don't know.
I used to make whipped cream.
It takes that long.
Maybe.
Oh, no.
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's try this once.
Just a little more.
Yes, yes, yes.
A little sweeter.
Sweet is okay.
I've heard it's better the sweeter it is.
Then add hot water.
But no.
Maybe there's something in there.
Let's get some hot water.
I'll get some coqui.
Okay, okay.
I'm making cupcakes today.
What? Why?
It's a special day, right? Girls' Day.
Oh, right! Thank you.
Hold on a second.
I'm so happy.
I'm ready!I'm so sorry!
I was going to make cupcakes today, but I don't have any cups!
I'm gonna go get some.
Cut!
What?
That's good.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm an honest person.
Honest boys.
Honest boys are good.
Honest boy.
And we're seriously going to wait and see once we're done.
We're all in trouble.
So we're screwing up?
We followed the recipe.
Oh, yeah?
Well, the ice is a little...
Three different colors?
There's four colors.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to handle the dough from the ball.
Here we go!
OK!
And then...
Yay!